<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-06T18:33:18+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Free crypto seriously</title><subtitle>A Blog about free bitcoins - faucets, watching adds, lotery etc.</subtitle><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why most of us are losing money in sports betting?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/06/why-we-are-mostly-loosing-betting.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why most of us are losing money in sports betting?" /><published>2020-12-06T09:23:45+01:00</published><updated>2020-12-06T09:23:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/12/06/why-we-are-mostly-loosing-betting</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/06/why-we-are-mostly-loosing-betting.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Sooner or later the vast majority of us have to ask the question -
    why we are losing money on betting in a long run?
    There is also an exception: people who do not track their progress or
    people with prolonged lucky season.
    However it does not change the fact - all betting offices prosper.
    While we, bettors need other jobs to finance our betting hobby.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The odds and their selection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There is wide spread misconception about how the betting odds are estimated.
    A lot of people still expect some individual human experts
    to determine the odds for the individual events directly in the betting office.
    However, this process is mainly done by third party companies who
    supply recommendations to the betting offices.
    Those companies are highly specialized in the field of modeling and prediction.
    They use the best state of the art tools to aggregate and interpolate the data
    for the best results achievable according to the known information.
    Furthermore, they have access to more information sources
    than we can even imagine.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    You can see this by comparison of the odds from various betting offices.
    The odds will be most likely very similar. The observable variance is mainly:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;different margin&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;special offer to attract customers&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;obvious errors - this is rare, but if you spot it,
            it is a good opportunity to profit&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    What does it mean for us? No matter how good is your knowledge
    of your favourite sport and how up-to-date are you information,
    you are still way behind your opponent. It is like playing sport against
    the ultimate all-time world master. No matter if you are junior player, or
    national level pro, you still have no chance.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;But they are exceptions!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Really? How many exceptions you can name?
    A lot of well know betting experts based their business about
    consulting or selling advices - instead of betting directly.
    That is quite suspicious.
    If you cannot win on betting, you can at least pretend you can win.
    If you gain trust of people, you can sell books, webinars and other
    stuff about betting. That seems to be quite a better idea than
    betting itself.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Now what to do?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Apparently there is not much space left to win in common betting.
    The possible opportunity to gain some edge over the betting offices
    could be on various weird events, weird sports, or weird bets.
    Keep in mind they need to pay for the intel.
    So the quality of intel they buy is determined by
    the quality they really require to get profit.
    They would not pay for extra precision if it is not worthy.
    So the less important bets could theoreticaly provide you
    with some room for profit. Of course, only in case you posses the
    ultimate expert knowledge of the topic.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Parimutuel betting - that is another story&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    In parimutuel betting, the odds are determined according
    to the actual value of the bets placed on the event outcomes.
    So the betting office does not control the odds, people who bet do.
    In most cases the odds converge to similar odds value like in a normal
    betting office. However, in some cases the people can
    move the odds in totally different direction. Good example is the
    US president election in 2020. The betting offices
    expect the Biden to win, while most people bet on Trump.
    That was a great opportunity to bet on Trump in average betting office,
    and also bet on Biden in parimutuel betting office at the same time.
    It would be profitable no matter the election result.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    According to the way how the parimutuel betting work, it gives
    you a possibly better chance to win.
    Your opponents there are not the top experts,
    but just a mass of weekend bettors with no deep knowledge.
    The bitcoin place where you can enjoy parimutuel betting is
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Sports betting is very difficult game.
    Your chances to success are not high, because you face an ultimate expert enemy.
    People who claim to success in this field are most likely faking
    to gain some additional benefit (sell consultations etc.).
    According to the theory, you have possibly a better chance
    on unusual sports and events.
    The betting game difficulty is probably lower with parimutuel betting.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Sooner or later the vast majority of us have to ask the question - why we are losing money on betting in a long run? There is also an exception: people who do not track their progress or people with prolonged lucky season. However it does not change the fact - all betting offices prosper. While we, bettors need other jobs to finance our betting hobby.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The whole truth about Honeygain</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/10/the_whole_truth_about_honeygain.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The whole truth about Honeygain" /><published>2020-11-10T09:55:23+01:00</published><updated>2020-11-10T09:55:23+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/11/10/the_whole_truth_about_honeygain</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/10/the_whole_truth_about_honeygain.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://r.honeygain.me/ELSPEFA544&quot;&gt;Honeygain&lt;/a&gt; is a platform designed
    to share your internet bandwidth for a reward.
    They offer a decent amount of money for running their applications
    on your devices.
    The application runs in the background and allow Honeygain
    to use your internet connection.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The whole idea is quite smart and it is similar to the TOR onion routers
    or similar solutions.
    However, there is also a dark side of this business.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Who and why needs your IP address?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    This is the first issue you should think about.
    Legit internet users do not need it at all.
    Does it mean that only criminals will use your connection?
    It is hard to say. But for sure we can conclude that your
    connection would not be used for a good purpose.
    In the best case, your connection will be used for abusing
    the terms and conditions of other services.
    For example: generating fake traffic, fake ads viewing,
    access to services from blacklisted and banned places.
    All of that is terribly bad.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Possible risks for you&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0006a.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    Now you know, only not really nice people want to use your network via
    Honeygain. What does it mean for you?
    Because you are the endpoint, it pretty much makes you responsible
    for their actions.
    The statement of Honeygain about this is quite clear. See their
    terms and conditions for answer:
    &lt;i&gt;it is the user who is responsible for its ability to share
        internet traffic and his compliance with local laws,
        regulations and agreements with third parties.&lt;/i&gt;
    I would strongly recommend to read the whole terms and conditions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    What could be the possible outcomes? The following
    list displays some of them (from the least devastating to
    the worst case scenarios):
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;getting banned on your favorite services (streaming, shopping...)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;disconnecting from the Internet by your provider&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;arrest for sharing highly illegal content&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    Now you probably ask how likely this can happen?
    I do not know. But they do not pay enough to make me test it.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Honeygain services are interesting and smart idea.
    However, it is mainly attractive only for illegal business partners.
    In case of problems, most likely you would be
    the responsible for every illegal activity done
    via your IP address. Because of that, I would
    not recommend to use this service at all.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Honeygain is a platform designed to share your internet bandwidth for a reward. They offer a decent amount of money for running their applications on your devices. The application runs in the background and allow Honeygain to use your internet connection. The whole idea is quite smart and it is similar to the TOR onion routers or similar solutions. However, there is also a dark side of this business. Who and why needs your IP address? This is the first issue you should think about. Legit internet users do not need it at all. Does it mean that only criminals will use your connection? It is hard to say. But for sure we can conclude that your connection would not be used for a good purpose. In the best case, your connection will be used for abusing the terms and conditions of other services. For example: generating fake traffic, fake ads viewing, access to services from blacklisted and banned places. All of that is terribly bad.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to spot a scam website</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/06/how_to_spot_a_scam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to spot a scam website" /><published>2020-11-06T16:10:01+01:00</published><updated>2020-11-06T16:10:01+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/11/06/how_to_spot_a_scam</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/06/how_to_spot_a_scam.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    The free crypto ecosystem is full of various scam attempts.
    Every day new scam websites are launched (see my list of
    &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/25/known_scams.html&quot;&gt;scam pages&lt;/a&gt;.
    The insane number of scam attempts can probably mean a bad thing -
    some of those little projects are successful.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    In this post I am revealing the basic principles how to recognize the obvious and
    not the so obvious scam websites.
    I investigate many scam sites and this post is describing the common
    features I have identified.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Unreal profit promises&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Probably the first and most easy thing you can check is what they are offering.
    If they offer too much too soon, it is definitely a scam, no matter what they argument.
    What is too much and what is reasonable?
    In the most of the world countries,
    the saving interests offered by regulated banks are below 1% per year.
    Keep in mind, the inflation is higher than that
    most of the time at the most of the countries.
    Some trustable crypto services offer much bigger interests.
    Commonly you can see something like 2-5% per year
    (&lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;,
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/join/cejnek_m&quot;&gt;Coinbase&lt;/a&gt;,
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.binance.com/en/register?ref=HXULRJ33&quot;&gt;Binance&lt;/a&gt;).
    There are some exceptions with interests close to 10% per year
    - mainly for stablecoins (&lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.com/exch/rqx87bbrmv&quot;&gt;Crypto.com&lt;/a&gt;).
    At this moment,
    I conclude that &lt;b&gt;everything above 10% per year is highly suspicious&lt;/b&gt;.
    If someone offers you 200% per year or 10% per week,
    you can be sure it is a joke or a scam.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Lack of transparency&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0005a.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    Scam projects rarely explain how they earn money to cover your earnings.
    The reason is simple. They do not explain, because
    there is nothing trustable to say, so they rather say nothing.
    I have not seen many scams trying to explain something to their users.
    But a few examples are worthy to mention:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
            &lt;i&gt;We are running money tumbler and we need many transactions to cover it.&lt;/i&gt;
            Although it sounds somehow trustable, it is not possible.
            Check the average prize of money tumbling services and you will see
            there is no chance they can earn that much money.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
            &lt;i&gt;It is the miracle of bitcoin mining.&lt;/i&gt; You need to be totally naive to
            trust this one. It is not even an explanation at all.
            There are no miracles in a real world, nor in bitcoin world.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;
            &lt;i&gt;It is really complicated and it cost us a lot of money to find out.
            We cannot tell our secrets to everyone.&lt;/i&gt;
            This lie is another scam gem. You are not asking for secrets.
            You are asking for basic information - and they should tell.
        &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    So the second sign of the scam website is a lack of explanation
    how they plan to make the miracle happen.
    &lt;b&gt;A project with a of lack transparency and/or explanation is most likely a scam.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Challenge for your impulsiveness&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Because the scam sites have nothing trustworthy to offer,
    they try to challenge you to take a risk.
    They say things that sound way too good to be truth.
    See some of their funny statements:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;It’s easier to earn on crypto investments then you think.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;It's time for simple and understandable solutions!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;All restrictions exist only in the minds of people.
            Maybe this is the only chance you get in your life.
Who knows? So ... act NOW !!!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Making money with us without expert knowledge is easier than you think. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    No matter how good those lies sounds, they are still lies.
    There are no shortcuts. Nobody will give you willingly something for free.
    If we analyze the scam statements closer, we can see some repeating patterns:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;We will give you a lot of money, even though you do not deserve it.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;You have to risk to gain (send us money), it is your last chance.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Sending money to us is not a risk.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    The lesson is simple. &lt;b&gt;Do not let them fool you&lt;/b&gt;. They are lying.
    It is their job to lie.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Positive reviews and evidence&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0005b.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    The problem with reviews is simple. The reviews are written by people.
    And some people can lie, while other people can trust false assumptions.
    So keep in mind, positive reviews does not mean anything.
    The portals displaying reviews are not working for a greater good,
    they are working for money instead.
    Also keep in mind, that picture or video is not a proof.
    Today, &lt;b&gt;anyone can fake any amount of evidence&lt;/b&gt;. Do not be stupid.
    Just because you or someone else would like to trust something, it does
    not become a truth.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
The major points of this post can be summarized as follows:
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;If something sounds good, it is a scam.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;If they cannot explain their business, they are scam.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not trust fake proofs.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not trust random reviews.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not risk nor guess, there is enough time to think and ask.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not be stupid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Best strategy for HI-LO game</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best strategy for HI-LO game" /><published>2020-11-03T16:35:55+01:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T16:35:55+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Many variants of HI-LO game occur on the free crypto ecosystem.
    Often the game is called directly the multiply game, or it is sorted in the
    multiply games category.
    The goal of this game is to make a binary (higher/lower than something) prediction
    about value of a random number.
    The most common variant of this game can be seen at
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; and
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://faucetpay.io/?r=713708&quot;&gt;FaucetPay&lt;/a&gt;.
    This game definitely belongs into the gambling category.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The main idea of this game is based on fact, that the game provider
    always give unfair odds. In other words - the range of winning numbers
    is always somehow smaller than the range of losing numbers.
    What does it mean? The loss is always more common than win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    On the internet, it is possible to find some tutorials how to beat this game.
    I analyze these tutorials theoretically and I also test them.
    Currently I can conclude, no one of them is working.
    And I can explain to you why they are not working at all.
    The only one viable existing approach
    how to deal with these games is presented in this post.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wrong idea 1: waiting for the right time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Some internet posts suggest to place a big bet after every series of losses.
    This approach is based on a wrong assumption,
    that the wins and losses are somehow evenly distributed in time
    and you can observe the imbalance of them.
    However that is not true.
    &lt;b&gt;Every new roll is completely independent from all others.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004a.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I will try to clarify it with a simple example.
    Imagine a fair coin - you have a chance to win exactly 50% of flips.
    You play this game for 1000 times and you luckily win all 1000 times!
    Now what is the probability you win also the next roll?
    It is again only 50%.
    The extreme luck of 1000 win strike imply nothing for the next roll.
    That is the sad true and there is nothing you can do abut that.
    In case you are in doubt, please make an experiment with a fair coin or a dice.
    You do not have to lost any money in gambling to figure that out the hard way.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wrong idea 2: double your bet after lost&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There is one street smart strategy popular in similar games.
    The strategy is based on recovering from your loses by
    betting more (typically doubling the bet) in the next round.
    Many people know this strategy, however no one has ever become rich.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004b.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    Simple example of this strategy follows. Again consider a fair coin.
    Bet 1 coin. If you win, bet again 1 coin. In case of lost,
    double your bet to 2 coins in order to recover from the previous lost in a next round.
    In case you lost 2 times in a row, bet 4 coins etc.
    So no matter how many times you lost, you get all coins back with the first win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    You can clearly see the point from the following figure.
    One game session is displayed in all three charts - the first two charts
    are details of the last one. The game session
    is done with 1000 coins and default bet of size 1 coin.
    The first chart displays only first 100 games.
    You can clearly see how look the pattern of bet increments.
    The first 100 games look pretty good for the player.
    And now the third chart, you can see that the number of coins
    is hitting really low values (much lower than our 1000 coins big stack).
    Every situation below zero means lost of everything and fatal end of the game.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004c.png&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    This strategy sounds perfect, so why it does not work?
    Because &lt;b&gt;you do not posses infinite number of coins&lt;/b&gt;.
    Sooner or later, you will get in a situation with too many lost games in a row
    and you will not have enough coins to cover it.
    It really does not matter how unlikely it sounds,
    it will happen and you cannot prevent it.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The correct approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Finally we are getting to the most important part of this post.
    Although now it seems impossible to beat this kind of games,
    there is something you can do.
    And this approach is called avoiding them.
    Simply avoid any game that you cannot win in a long run.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I am pretty sure, some of you now have the idea - what about not playing the
    game in a long run?
    What about all those people who won a lottery?
    Do not confuse lucky and smart - it is not similar in any way.
    The problem is that your life is full of decisions.
    Basically every decision you make is a part of long run decision making sequence.
    So to be successful in any game, field, or whole life - you need
    to limit all those decisions that does not pay off in the long run.
    Again, if you are in doubt, run experiments.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conslusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Do not trust the scam bloggers of the Internet and their magical approaches
    how to beat unbeatable games. They are incredibly stupid, or they have
    some profit from your improper action (they invite you via referral to the game etc.).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Finally I should have mention one exception from the &lt;i&gt;never play this game&lt;/i&gt; rule.
    And this is fun. If you do gambling for fun and you
    are ok to lost your money, then go wild.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Many variants of HI-LO game occur on the free crypto ecosystem. Often the game is called directly the multiply game, or it is sorted in the multiply games category. The goal of this game is to make a binary (higher/lower than something) prediction about value of a random number. The most common variant of this game can be seen at freebitco.in and FaucetPay. This game definitely belongs into the gambling category. The main idea of this game is based on fact, that the game provider always give unfair odds. In other words - the range of winning numbers is always somehow smaller than the range of losing numbers. What does it mean? The loss is always more common than win. On the internet, it is possible to find some tutorials how to beat this game. I analyze these tutorials theoretically and I also test them. Currently I can conclude, no one of them is working. And I can explain to you why they are not working at all. The only one viable existing approach how to deal with these games is presented in this post.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The best free crypto pages of the year 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The best free crypto pages of the year 2020" /><published>2020-10-27T07:13:12+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-27T07:13:12+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;
    The best crypto websites recommended to earn free crypto in 2020 are introduced here.
    All pages mentioned here are considered to be legit.
    However, keep in mind, they are not regulated,
    so you never know when they disappear.
    This post will be updated regularly during the year 2020.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The ordered list of the recommended websites (from the best) follows:
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. freebitco.in&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is featuring generous free faucet,
multiply game, two lotteries, betting, interest savings and referral program. They allow to use adblock.
Best option for the most crypto claimers. I wrote more about this website in a separated
    &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Coinpayu&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinpayu.com/?r=Bankok1&quot;&gt;Coinpayu&lt;/a&gt; is offering watching ads
    in exchange for satoshi reward. They provide enough ads to earn about 100-400 satoshi
    per day (about 30 minutes watching).
    They are also featuring referral program including referral market.
    Furthermore, they arrange various offers from the other providers (paid surveys etc.).
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. adbtc&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://r.adbtc.top/1930435&quot;&gt;adbtc&lt;/a&gt; is ads based free
    bitcoin site similar to Coinpayu. Their ads are not too invasive
    and the rewards are quite good. They also feature referral market
    and low paying faucet.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;4. Faucet Crypto&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.faucetcrypto.com/ref/487446&quot;&gt;Faucet Crypto&lt;/a&gt;
    is a free bitcoin site similar to Coinpayu. It also offers:
    offerwall, watching ads and referral program. Furthermore, this
    site features a level system.
    You can gain user levels according to you activity on the site.
    Higher levels bring bonuses to you.
    On the other hand, this site is invasive with its ads and the time counters
    works only if the browser tab has a full focus. That is quite annoying.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;5. FaucetPay&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://faucetpay.io/?r=713708&quot;&gt;FaucetPay&lt;/a&gt; is primarily a
    micropayment wallet and earning platform.
    In other words they help you to collect small amount of crypto from other sites
    without high transaction fee. They also feature: daily free faucet,
    multiply btc gambling games, referral program and exchange.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;6. Cointiply&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;http://cointiply.com/r/zk8vk&quot;&gt;Cointiply&lt;/a&gt; is yet another site
    offering free faucet, referral program and offerwall.
    They are pretty much similar to the
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.faucetcrypto.com/ref/487446&quot;&gt;Faucet Crypto&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;7. BTCspinner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://btcspinner.io/invite/945341&quot;&gt;BTCspinner&lt;/a&gt; is featuring a game
    (browser fidged spinner), free faucet (every 30 minutes) and referral program.
    The spinner can be fun for a while, but it is not paying much. Adblock is allowed
    on this site.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">The best crypto websites recommended to earn free crypto in 2020 are introduced here. All pages mentioned here are considered to be legit. However, keep in mind, they are not regulated, so you never know when they disappear. This post will be updated regularly during the year 2020. The ordered list of the recommended websites (from the best) follows:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A great review of freebitco.in</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A great review of freebitco.in" /><published>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html">&lt;p&gt;
    I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features.
    I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind,
    this post can be updated in future.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Is the site legit?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    According to my tests (deposit/withdraw), the &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is legit.
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is on the market for many years.
    During all my tests and experiments, I have not noticed anything suspicious.
    All of their features have reasonable parameters - they are not promising miracles.
    Also, they are very transparent and their games can be classified as a provably fair.
    I also wrote a Python script to replicate the random number generation process from
    server and user hash and I have to admit it is fair.
    They responded to my emails promptly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Free faucet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The amount of BTC you can get from their
    faucet is derived from the value of the USD.
    The biggest price you can get is the BTC equivalent of $200.
    Every time you roll the faucet you have a chance 1:10000 to get the maximal price.
    There are also other bigger prices with various
    chances for success.
    The lowest price is approximately 0.002 USD. You can roll the faucet every 60 minutes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    How much can you get? In case you roll 10k times with an average luck
    (your rolls contain every possible
    number 1-1000 exactly once),
    then you win $270 worth in BTC. So in case you
    roll ten times per day,
    you get $270 in about 1k days (less than 3 years),
    or in other words $0.27 per day. Keep in mind that these
    numbers are
    average estimate for person with average luck in a long run.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Multiply BTC - HI-LO game &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Their multiply BTC feature is traditional HI-LO game
    with quite a sophisticated interface.
    The rolls are fair. You can validate each roll
    according to the server hash. However,
    no matter what settings you use, the game is set to return
    back to the users only only fraction of the bets.
    If you set the game to coin flip mode, you will get only 47.5% winning
    chance. You would need 50% to stay even. So there is no chance to win
    in a long run with an average luck.
    More information about the HI-LO game in general
    is my other &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Earn - interest savings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Every balance higher than 30k satoshi is automatically increased daily.
Currently the earning rate is set to 4.08% yearly,
so it is roughly 1 satoshi per day for every 10k satoshi you have.
The interest rate is similar to other legit services, so I would trust it is not a scam trick.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Lottery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There are actually two lotteries.
    You can buy or obtain tickets as a reward for using their features.
    However the lotteries are not worthy in a long run.
    The prize of a ticket is higher than an expected value.
    In other words, you pay more than you can actually win.
    The lottery is good only for fun.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Betting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    features quite a unique parimutuel betting option.
    The odds are set according to the pool size of the bet options.
    Example: if the most users bet on team A,
    you can get a much better odd on the team B.
    In common betting office you get odds according
    to an extremely precise prediction model, so you have
    a very little chance to win something in a long run.
    However, with the parimutuel betting the odds
    are given by actual bettors.
    Thus, if you understand any topic - sport, politics etc. better
    than other people do, you should definitely try betting via
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I randomly bet on random topics for more than 150+ times on
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    with outcome close to 0. Thus, I assume that their fee is low
    and the winners are paid fairly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Referral program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; has probably the
    best referral program I have ever seen:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;50% of your referral free rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;reward points for referral bets, hi-lo rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;25% commissions on any interest earned by your referrals&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    Furthermore, you can reward your referrals with share from your profits.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reward program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    also features interesting reward program. They pay you with reward points
    almost for every action you do (or your referrals do).
    You exchange the reward points for various prizes,
    or you can change them for BTC
    - one reward point is equal to one satoshi.
    Keep in mind that the exchange for BTC is
    possible only if you collect at least 100k of reward points.
    Also, if you play free faucet more
    than 12 times per day, it is worthy to buy the reward
    point booster. You can buy this booster
    for 1200 reward points, and it grants you 100 extra
    points for every free roll.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Recommended strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    To gain as much as possible via
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; I would
    recommend:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;roll faucet as often as possible&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;bet on events if you have the skill
    and knowledge to beat other players&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;choose to get reward points instead of lottery
            tickets in your profile settings
            (go to PROFILE/DISABLE LOTTERY &amp; INTEREST/check DISABLE LOTTERY)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;collect reward points and exchange them for BTC&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;strictly avoid the lottery and hi-lo game&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;get some active referrals&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Pros:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a decent faucet that pays, if you are consistent and diligent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They feature unique betting system than can be highly productive - depends on your skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Their referral program is just awesome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They automatically give you interest if you have more than 30k satoshi&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;They are not living from ads, so they do not force you to observe junk ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;H3&gt;Cons:&lt;/H3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HI-LO game - this game is good for fun, but you cannot actually win in a long run.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lottery - the tickets are not worthy in the long run (like with every lottery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I would strongly recommend to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
as a viable option in your free BTC site portfolio.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features. I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind, this post can be updated in future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">List of obvious scams</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="List of obvious scams" /><published>2020-10-25T12:10:15+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-25T12:10:15+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams.html">&lt;p&gt;
    The pages listed below are obviously scam.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Active scams&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    Last check was done at 2020/12/06.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;paydec.net&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 0 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinovu.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 0 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bucksbitco.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 5 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;coinload.cash&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 11 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;crypto-samurai.org&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 14 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;doublebitcoin.vip&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 14 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;goldchinapro.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 17 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bnktothefuture.biz&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 17 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;goldenwaves.biz&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 18 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;ebitcoino.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 18 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;vip7crypto.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 18 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;deeptradebot.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;crypto-modern.ltd&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitquali.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;imining.pro&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;stabmining.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;coinentrust.io&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 23 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitdogy.top&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;crypto-tower.org&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;coin-busines.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;infojob.xyz&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;investmentkingdom.io&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitbinary.net&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;spacemining.live&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 25 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;aynamining.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 26 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;c7earn.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 26 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;angelicage.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 26 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;www.purplemining.ltd&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;arbirate.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;credabitcoin.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;kinginvesto.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;chainmoneys.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;cryptoware.biz&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 27 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoin-guards.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;royalbtc.xyz&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;jampsixdollar.pw&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;eth-finance.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoin-double.cc&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;btcmillionaire.io&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;miningbase.cloud&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;oilsupergold.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;ad-country.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;korean-gold.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Coinwintrade.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinfibers.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinworldwide.live&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;falcon-golden.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;btc-10.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;tozzu.io&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;easycashbux.com/betfury&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;exchange-rates.top&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;hourpaysystem.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;legithourpay.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;faucet-guide.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;limited-bitcoin-generator.org&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 28 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;lucrative-shares.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 34 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;btc-go.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 37 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;elios.ltd&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 37 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;xdoubler.com&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 65 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;multim.io&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 69 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;coinbit.cash&lt;/i&gt;, online at least 117 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;





If you want to report another scam,
please drop me an email:
&lt;a href=&quot;email:elspethrooneyprinceofparty@gmail.com&quot;&gt;elspethrooneyprinceofparty@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">The pages listed below are obviously scam.</summary></entry></feed>