<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-27T14:56:46+01:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Free BTC seriously</title><subtitle>A Blog about free bitcoins - faucets, watching adds, lotery etc.</subtitle><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><entry><title type="html">A great review of freebitco.in</title><link href="/2020/10/27/freebitcoin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A great review of freebitco.in" /><published>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</updated><id>/2020/10/27/freebitcoin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/10/27/freebitcoin.html">&lt;p&gt;
    I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features.
    I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind,
    this post can be updated in future.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Is the site legit?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    According to my tests (deposit/withdraw), the &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is legit.
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is on the market for many years.
    During all my tests and experiments, I have not noticed anything suspicious.
    All of their features has reasonable parameters - they are not promising miracles.
    Also they are very transparent and their games can be classified as a provably fair.
    I also wrote Python script to replicate the random number generation process from
    server and user hash and I have to admit it is fair.
    They responded to my emails promptly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Free faucet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The amount of BTC you can get from their faucet is derived from the value of USD.
    The biggest price you can get is BTC equivalent of $200.
    Every time you roll the faucet you have a chance 1:10000 to get the maximal price.
    There are also other bigger prices with various chances to success.
    The lowest price is approximately 0.002 USD. You can roll the faucet every 60 minutes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    How much you get? In case you roll 10k times with average luck
    (you roll get every possible number 1-1000 exactly once), then you win $270 worth in BTC. So in case you roll ten times per day,
    you get $270 in about 1k days (less than 3 years), or in other words $0.27 per day. Keep in mind that these numbers are
    estimate for person with average luck in long run.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Multiply BTC - HI-LO game &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Their multiply BTC feature is traditional HI-LO game with quite a sophisticated interface.
The rolls are fair. You can validate each roll according to the server hash. However,
no matter what settings you use, the game is set
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Earn - interest savings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Every balance higher than 30k satoshi is automatically increased daily.
Currently the earning rate is set to 4.08% yearly,
so it is roughly 1 satoshi for every 10k satoshi you have per day.
The interest rate is similar to other legit services, so I would trust it is not a scam trick.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Lottery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
There are actually two lotteries. You can buy or obtain tickets as reward for using their features.
However the lotteries are not worthy in a long run - the tickets you need to win with average luck
are way more expensive than prizes you can win. The lottery is good only for fun.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Betting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; features quite an unique
perimutuel betting option. The odds are set according to the pool size of the bet options.
Example: if the most users bet on team A, you can get a much better odd on the team B.
In common betting office you get odds according to an extremely precise prediction model, so you have
a very little chance to win something in a long run. However, with the perimutuel betting the odds
are given by actual bettors. Thus if you understand any topic - sport, politics etc. better
than other people do, you should definitely try betting via
&lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I randomly bet on random topics 150+ times on
&lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
with outcome close to 0. Thus I assume that their fee is low and the winners are payed fairly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Referral program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; has probably the
    best referral program I have ever seen:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;50% of your referral free rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;reward points for referral bets, hi-lo rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;25% commissions on any interest earned by your referrals&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    Furthermore, you can reward your referrals with share from your profits.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reward program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; also features interesting
    reward program. They pay you with reward points almost for every action you do (or your refferals do).
    You exchange the reward points for various prizes, or you can change them for BTC
    - one reward points is equal to one satoshi. Keep in mind that the exchange for BTC is
    possible only if you collect at least 100k of reward points. Also if you play free faucet more
    than 12 times per day, is worthy to buy the reward point booster. You can buy this booster
    for 1200 reward points, and it grants you 100 extra points for every free roll.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Recommended strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
To gain as much as possible via &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; I would
recommend:
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;roll faucet as often as possible&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;you can bet on events if you have the skill
and knowledge to beat other players&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;choose to get reward points instead of lottery tickets in settings&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;collect reward points and exchange them for BTC&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;strictly avoid the lottery and hi-lo game&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;get some active referrals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Pros:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a decent faucet that pays, if you are consistent and diligent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They feature unique betting system than can be highly productive - depends on your skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They referral program is just awesome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They automatically give you interest if you have more than 30k satoshi&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;They are not living from ads, so they do not force to observe junk ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;H3&gt;Cons:&lt;/H3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HI-LO game - this game is good for fun, but you cannot actually win in a long run.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lottery - the tickets are not worthy in the long run (like with every lotery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
I would strongly recommend to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
as a viable option in your free BTC site portfolio.</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features. I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind, this post can be updated in future.</summary></entry></feed>