<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-03T20:09:41+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Free crypto seriously</title><subtitle>A Blog about free bitcoins - faucets, watching adds, lotery etc.</subtitle><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><entry><title type="html">Best strategy for HI-LO game</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best strategy for HI-LO game" /><published>2020-11-03T16:35:55+01:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T16:35:55+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html">&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Many variants of HI-LO game occur on the free crypto ecosystem.
    Often the game is called directly the multiply game, or it is sorted in the
    multiply games category.
    The goal of this game is to make a binary (higher/lower than something) prediction
    about value of a random number.
    The most common variant of this game can be seen at
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; and
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://faucetpay.io/?r=713708&quot;&gt;FaucetPay&lt;/a&gt;.
    This game definitely belongs into the gambling category.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The main idea of this game is based on fact, that the game provider
    always give unfair odds. In other words - the range of winning numbers
    is always somehow smaller than the range of losing numbers.
    What does it mean? The loss is always more common than win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    On the internet, it is possible to find some tutorials how to beat this game.
    I analyze these tutorials theoretically and I also test them.
    Currently I can conclude, no one of them is working.
    And I can explain to you why they are not working at all.
    The only one viable existing approach
    how to deal with these games is presented in this post.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wrong idea 1: waiting for the right time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Some internet posts suggest to place a big bet after every series of losses.
    This approach is based on a wrong assumption,
    that the wins and losses are somehow evenly distributed in time
    and you can observe the imbalance of them.
    However that is not true.
    &lt;b&gt;Every new roll is completely independent from all others.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004a.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I will try to clarify it with a simple example.
    Imagine a fair coin - you have a chance to win exactly 50% of flips.
    You play this game for 1000 times and you luckily win all 1000 times!
    Now what is the probability you win also the next roll?
    It is again only 50%.
    The extreme luck of 1000 win strike imply nothing for the next roll.
    That is the sad true and there is nothing you can do abut that.
    In case you are in doubt, please make an experiment with a fair coin or a dice.
    You do not have to lost any money in gambling to figure that out the hard way.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wrong idea 2: double your bet after lost&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There is one street smart strategy popular in similar games.
    The strategy is based on recovering from your loses by
    betting more (typically doubling the bet) in the next round.
    Many people know this strategy, however no one has ever become rich.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004b.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    Simple example of this strategy follows. Again consider a fair coin.
    Bet 1 coin. If you win, bet again 1 coin. In case of lost,
    double your bet to 2 coins in order to recover from the previous lost in a next round.
    In case you lost 2 times in a row, bet 4 coins etc.
    So no matter how many times you lost, you get all coins back with the first win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    You can clearly see the point from the following figure.
    One game session is displayed in all three charts - the first two charts
    are details of the last one. The game session
    is done with 1000 coins and default bet of size 1 coin.
    The first chart displays only first 100 games.
    You can clearly see how look the pattern of bet increments.
    The first 100 games look pretty good for the player.
    And now the third chart, you can see that the number of coins
    is hitting really low values (much lower than our 1000 coins big stack).
    Every situation below zero means lost of everything and fatal end of the game.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;in_post&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/0004c.png&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    This strategy sounds perfect, so why it does not work?
    Because &lt;b&gt;you do not posses infinite number of coins&lt;/b&gt;.
    Sooner or later, you will get in a situation with too many lost games in a row
    and you will not have enough coins to cover it.
    It really does not matter how unlikely it sounds,
    it will happen and you cannot prevent it.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The correct approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Finally we are getting to the most important part of this post.
    Although now it seems impossible to beat this kind of games,
    there is something you can do.
    And this approach is called avoiding them.
    Simply avoid any game that you cannot win in a long run.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I am pretty sure, some of you now have the idea - what about not playing the
    game in a long run?
    What about all those people who won a lottery?
    Do not confuse lucky and smart - it is not similar in any way.
    The problem is that your life is full of decisions.
    Basically every decision you make is a part of long run decision making sequence.
    So to be successful in any game, field, or whole life - you need
    to limit all those decisions that does not pay off in the long run.
    Again, if you are in doubt, run experiments.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conslusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Do not trust the scam bloggers of the Internet and their magical approaches
    how to beat unbeatable games. They are incredibly stupid, or they have
    some profit from your improper action (they invite you via referral to the game etc.).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Finally I should have mention one exception from the &lt;i&gt;never play this game&lt;/i&gt; rule.
    And this is fun. If you do gambling for fun and you
    are ok to lost your money, then go wild.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Many variants of HI-LO game occur on the free crypto ecosystem. Often the game is called directly the multiply game, or it is sorted in the multiply games category. The goal of this game is to make a binary (higher/lower than something) prediction about value of a random number. The most common variant of this game can be seen at freebitco.in and FaucetPay. This game definitely belongs into the gambling category. The main idea of this game is based on fact, that the game provider always give unfair odds. In other words - the range of winning numbers is always somehow smaller than the range of losing numbers. What does it mean? The loss is always more common than win. On the internet, it is possible to find some tutorials how to beat this game. I analyze these tutorials theoretically and I also test them. Currently I can conclude, no one of them is working. And I can explain to you why they are not working at all. The only one viable existing approach how to deal with these games is presented in this post.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The best free crypto pages of the year 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The best free crypto pages of the year 2020" /><published>2020-10-27T07:13:12+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-27T07:13:12+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/the-best-free-crypto-pages-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;
    The best crypto websites recommended to earn free crypto in 2020 are introduced here.
    All pages mentioned here are considered to be legit.
    However, keep in mind, they are not regulated,
    so you never know when they disappear.
    This post will be updated regularly during the year 2020.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The ordered list of the recommended websites (from the best) follows:
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. freebitco.in&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is featuring generous free faucet,
multiply game, two lotteries, betting, interest savings and referral program. They allow to use adblock.
Best option for the most crypto claimers. I wrote more about this website in a separated
    &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Coinpayu&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinpayu.com/?r=Bankok1&quot;&gt;Coinpayu&lt;/a&gt; is offering watching ads
    in exchange for satoshi reward. They provide enough ads to earn about 100-400 satoshi
    per day (about 30 minutes watching).
    They are also featuring referral program including referral market.
    Furthermore, they arrange various offers from the other providers (paid surveys etc.).
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. Faucet Crypto&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.faucetcrypto.com/ref/487446&quot;&gt;Faucet Crypto&lt;/a&gt;
    is a free bitcoin site similar to Coinpayu. It also offers:
    offerwall, watching ads and referral program. Furthermore, this
    site features a level system.
    You can gain user levels according to you activity on the site.
    Higher levels bring bonuses to you.
    On the other hand, this site is invasive with its ads and the time counters
    works only if the browser tab has a full focus. That is quite annoying.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. FaucetPay&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://faucetpay.io/?r=713708&quot;&gt;FaucetPay&lt;/a&gt; is primarily a
    micropayment wallet and earning platform.
    In other words they help you to collect small amount of crypto from other sites
    without high transaction fee. They also feature: daily free faucet,
    multiply btc gambling games, referral program and exchange.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5. Cointiply&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;http://cointiply.com/r/zk8vk&quot;&gt;Cointiply&lt;/a&gt; is yet another site
    offering free faucet, referral program and offerwall.
    They are pretty much similar to the
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.faucetcrypto.com/ref/487446&quot;&gt;Faucet Crypto&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;6. BTCspinner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://btcspinner.io/invite/945341&quot;&gt;BTCspinner&lt;/a&gt; is featuring a game
    (browser fidged spinner), free faucet (every 30 minutes) and referral program.
    The spinner can be fun for a while, but it is not paying much. Adblock is allowed
    on this site.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">The best crypto websites recommended to earn free crypto in 2020 are introduced here. All pages mentioned here are considered to be legit. However, keep in mind, they are not regulated, so you never know when they disappear. This post will be updated regularly during the year 2020. The ordered list of the recommended websites (from the best) follows:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A great review of freebitco.in</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A great review of freebitco.in" /><published>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-27T00:45:13+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/27/a_great_review_of_freebitcoin.html">&lt;p&gt;
    I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features.
    I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind,
    this post can be updated in future.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Is the site legit?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    According to my tests (deposit/withdraw), the &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is legit.
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; is on the market for many years.
    During all my tests and experiments, I have not noticed anything suspicious.
    All of their features has reasonable parameters - they are not promising miracles.
    Also they are very transparent and their games can be classified as a provably fair.
    I also wrote Python script to replicate the random number generation process from
    server and user hash and I have to admit it is fair.
    They responded to my emails promptly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Free faucet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The amount of BTC you can get from their faucet is derived from the value of USD.
    The biggest price you can get is BTC equivalent of $200.
    Every time you roll the faucet you have a chance 1:10000 to get the maximal price.
    There are also other bigger prices with various chances to success.
    The lowest price is approximately 0.002 USD. You can roll the faucet every 60 minutes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    How much can you get? In case you roll 10k times with an average luck
    (your rolls contain every possible number 1-1000 exactly once),
    then you win $270 worth in BTC. So in case you roll ten times per day,
    you get $270 in about 1k days (less than 3 years),
    or in other words $0.27 per day. Keep in mind that these numbers are
    average estimate for person with average luck in a long run.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Multiply BTC - HI-LO game &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Their multiply BTC feature is traditional HI-LO game
    with quite a sophisticated interface.
    The rolls are fair. You can validate each roll
    according to the server hash. However,
    no matter what settings you use, the game is set to return
    back to the users only only fraction of the bets.
    If you set the game to coin flip mode, you will get only 47.5% winning
    chance. You would need 50% to stay even. So there is no chance to win
    in a long run with an average luck.
    More information about the HI-LO game in general
    is my other &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/03/hi-lo-games.html&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Earn - interest savings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Every balance higher than 30k satoshi is automatically increased daily.
Currently the earning rate is set to 4.08% yearly,
so it is roughly 1 satoshi per day for every 10k satoshi you have.
The interest rate is similar to other legit services, so I would trust it is not a scam trick.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Lottery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There are actually two lotteries.
    You can buy or obtain tickets as reward for using their features.
    However the lotteries are not worthy in a long run.
    The prize of ticket is higher than an expected value.
    In other words, you pay more than you can actually win.
    The lottery is good only for fun.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Betting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    features quite an unique perimutuel betting option.
    The odds are set according to the pool size of the bet options.
    Example: if the most users bet on team A,
    you can get a much better odd on the team B.
    In common betting office you get odds according
    to an extremely precise prediction model, so you have
    a very little chance to win something in a long run.
    However, with the perimutuel betting the odds
    are given by actual bettors.
    Thus if you understand any topic - sport, politics etc. better
    than other people do, you should definitely try betting via
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I randomly bet on random topics for more than 150+ times on
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    with outcome close to 0. Thus I assume that their fee is low
    and the winners are payed fairly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Referral program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; has probably the
    best referral program I have ever seen:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;50% of your referral free rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;reward points for referral bets, hi-lo rolls&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;25% commissions on any interest earned by your referrals&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    Furthermore, you can reward your referrals with share from your profits.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reward program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
    also features interesting reward program. They pay you with reward points
    almost for every action you do (or your referrals do).
    You exchange the reward points for various prizes,
    or you can change them for BTC
    - one reward points is equal to one satoshi.
    Keep in mind that the exchange for BTC is
    possible only if you collect at least 100k of reward points.
    Also if you play free faucet more
    than 12 times per day, it is worthy to buy the reward
    point booster. You can buy this booster
    for 1200 reward points, and it grants you 100 extra
    points for every free roll.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Recommended strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    To gain as much as possible via
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt; I would
    recommend:
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;roll faucet as often as possible&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;bet on events if you have the skill
    and knowledge to beat other players&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;choose to get reward points instead of lottery
            tickets in your profile settings
            (go to PROFILE/DISABLE LOTTERY &amp; INTEREST/check DISABLE LOTTERY)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;collect reward points and exchange them for BTC&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;strictly avoid the lottery and hi-lo game&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;get some active referrals&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Pros:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a decent faucet that pays, if you are consistent and diligent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They feature unique betting system than can be highly productive - depends on your skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Their referral program is just awesome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They automatically give you interest if you have more than 30k satoshi&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;They are not living from ads, so they do not force you to observe junk ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;H3&gt;Cons:&lt;/H3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HI-LO game - this game is good for fun, but you cannot actually win in a long run.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lottery - the tickets are not worthy in the long run (like with every lottery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I would strongly recommend to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://freebitco.in/?r=38728911&quot;&gt;freebitco.in&lt;/a&gt;
as a viable option in your free BTC site portfolio.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">I have tested this faucet site for a few months. I analyzed all of their features. I have to conclude that I would recommend this site. Keep in mind, this post can be updated in future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">List of obvious scams</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="List of obvious scams" /><published>2020-10-25T12:10:15+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-25T12:10:15+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/25/known_scams.html">&lt;p&gt;
    The pages listed below are obviously scam.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Active scams&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;tozzu.io&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;btc-10.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;falcon-golden.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;houratm.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;crypto-riches.ltd&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;btc-go.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinfibers.com&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinworldwide.live&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcoinsquare.best&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;bitcong.us&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Coinwintrade.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;cryptotwister.io&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;korean-gold.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;ad-country.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;oilsupergold.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;keyaco.net&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;cashmix.io&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;miningbase.cloud&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

If you want to report another scam,
please drop me an email:
&lt;a href=&quot;email:elspethrooneyprinceofparty@gmail.com&quot;&gt;elspethrooneyprinceofparty@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.</content><author><name>Elspeth Rooney</name></author><summary type="html">The pages listed below are obviously scam.</summary></entry></feed>